Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Institute of Visual Art Records, 1962-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1962-2003
  - 2. Administrative Files, 1962-2003
    - Gallery, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Gallery Committee
      - 1988-1993 (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
      - Art History, 1981-1995 (Box 21, Folder 17-19)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Gallery Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 21, Folder 21-22)
    - Garguilo, Domenico (called Micco Spadaro), 1968 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Gershan, Lester M., 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 24-25)
    - Gertler, Coleman, Gift, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Gift Acknowledgement, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Gollin, Hanna R., 1984 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Granik, Arthur, Gift, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Green Hall
      - Basement, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - Construction and Remodeling, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 31)
      - Gallery Remodeling, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 32)
      - Summer, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - Tours, 1972-1977 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Haas, Richard, UWM Alum/Gifts, 1984-1993 (Box 21, Folder 35-36)
    - Hara, Keiko, UWM Alum, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Hesenhoeft, Ralph, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Human Resources, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Inter-Arts Gallery Committee, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Jacobson, Sheba, Gift, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Janis, Sidney, Gallery, Rug Photographs, undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Jiao Tong University, Shanghai, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - John Michael Kohler Arts Center, Sheboygan, WI, 1983-1987 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Johnston Gift, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Katchuk, Gleb and Olga Kashumbe-Kove, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Kohl, Sidney, Gift, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Krikonian, Robert, Gifts, 1973-1987 (Box 21, Folder 48-50)
    - Lacktman, Michael, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Laskin, Myron, Gift, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Layton, Frederick, Endowment and Gallery, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Levy, Don, Donation, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Liebman Lectures, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Liebman, William L., Gift, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Maher III, J. Thomas, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Manning, Per, 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Meyer, Martine Darmon, Donation, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Mid-America College Art Association Conference (MACAA), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 60-61)
    - Midwest Museum Conference, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964-1985 (Box 21, Folder 63-64)
    - Moebius, Carl W. and Janet S. Gifts, 1985-1995 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    - Moebius, Carl, John Silbar, and Sidney Kohl, Gifts, 1975-1981 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Molina, Carlos Julio, 1995-1999 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Museum Librarianship, 1969-1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Museum Policy Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
    - Museum Studies
      - 1968-1975 (Box 22, Folder 9-10)
      - UWM Anthropology, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Museum Training Proposal, UWM, 1965-1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Neuenschwander, Rivane, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Neumann, Mary Wilson von, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Newsletter Photographs, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Occupation, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Oeder, Gary M., Gift, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - PA Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Pelikan, A.G., Gift, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Permanent Collection, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Pettit, Lloyd, Gift, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Photo Essay Exhibition, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Planning Document, 1983-1986 (Box 22, Folder 23-24)
    - Planning, Policy, Grants, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Policy Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 26-27)
    - Pomerantz, Louis, Lecture and Workshops, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Pottinger, Donald, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Press Release, 1983-1993 (Box 22, Folder 30-32)
    - Priebe, Karl, Gift, 1964-1973 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Publicity, 1984-1991 (Box 22, Folder 34-36)
    - Ramirez, Chuck, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Rand, Harry, Lecture, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Rental of Artwork, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Rieley, James, Donation, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Ritz Gift, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Ritzenthaler, Estate of, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Robers, Caryl, Gift, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Rogers Collection
      - 1965-1992 (Box 22, Folder 444-46)
      - Catalog, undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 48)
      - Installation Photos, undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
      - Labels and Case Titles, undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
      - Loan Extension, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 51)
      - Old Catalogue, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 52)
      - Photograph, undated (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Rojtman Lecture Series, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - "Roland Barthes", 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Romine, Laura Estabrook, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Rosenberg Collection
      - 1974-1984 (Box 22, Folder 57-58)
      - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 59)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 60)
      - Rosenberg, Blanche, Estate, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - Rosenblum, Robert, Lecture, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - Rubinstein, Bert, Gift, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - Salabarrias, Aaron, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Sarcevic, Bojan, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Schellin, Ruth, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Schenk, Quentin F. and Emmy Lou, 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
    - School of Architecture
      - 1987 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Frank Lloyd Wright, 1981-1992 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - School of Fine Arts Planning Document, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Seaman, Douglas, 1987-1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Shuman, Everett C., 1985-1988 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Sihare, Lazmi Prasad, Lecture, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Skolnik, Abraham and Merle, Estates Gift, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Slides, 1971-1995 (Box 23, Folder 13-19)
    - Smith, Mary, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Michael, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Singer Jr, Sidney, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Singru, Shilpa, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Stinchfield 1993.3, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Stolen Art Work, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Straus, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Strothman, E.P., 1983-1987 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Summer, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Taylor, John Lloyd, 1971-1988 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Teweles, William, Donation, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - The Artist and the Quilt, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Thiesen, Adeline, Estate Donation, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Treul, William, Loan, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Uihlein House Collection, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Ullman, Paul, Donation, 1984-1999 (Box 23, Folder 36-37)
    - UWM Art Museum
      - Exhibition Schedule, 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 38-40)
      - Inventory, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 42-43)
      - Operations, 1983-1990 (Box 23, Folder 44-50)
      - Planning Document, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - Policies and Guidelines, 1984-1988 (Box 23, Folder 52)
      - Policy Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 53)
      - Policy Statement and Planning Document, 1985-1991 (Box 23, Folder 54)
      - Volunteer Project, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Van Arsdale, 1974-1978 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Vogel Hall Building and Remodeling, 1980-1984 (Box 23, Folder 57-58)
    - Vogele, Bruce and Vibeke, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 59-60)
    - Wiley, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - Wisconsin Arts Boards Panel, 1981-1986 (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Women's Autobiographical Artists' Books (WAAB)
      - Administrative
        - Artworks Gallery, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - General WAAB Files, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3-6)
        - Hoffberg, Judith, As Lender, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Lenders, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 8)
        - Loans, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - Publicity, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
        - Sackner, Marvin, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
        - School of the Art Institute, Chicago, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 12)
        - UWM Library, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 13)
        - Zwehl-Burke, Pamela, As Lender, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Artists
        - Antin, Eleanor, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 15)
        - Azara, Nancy, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 16)
        - Baker, Susan, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 17)
        - Barkus, Mariona, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 18)
        - Beckman, Laurel, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 19)
        - Berry, Carolyn, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 20)
        - Caroompass, Carole, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 21)
        - Daw, Leila, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 22)
        - Davila, Maritza, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 23)
        - Degener, Amanda, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 24)
        - DeGenevieve, Barbara, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 25)
        - Dove, Pauline, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 26)
        - Drucker, Barbara, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 27)
        - Edelson, Mary Beth, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 28)
        - Ellis, Eddie, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 29)
        - Forti, Simone, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 30)
        - Freeman, Jane, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 31)
        - Geib, Dona, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 32)
        - Grant, Susan Kae, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 33)
        - Hackman, Vida, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 34)
        - Heft, Caren, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 35)
        - Henes, Donna, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 36)
        - Hershman, Lynn, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 37)
        - Holt, Nancy, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 38)
        - Jackson, Sarah, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 39)
        - King, Susan, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 40)
        - Kingsbury, Anne, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 41)
        - Knowles, Alison, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 42)
        - Kruger, Barbara, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 43)
        - Lacy, Suzanne, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 44)
        - Lakich, Lily, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 45)
        - Larson, Dara, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 46)
        - Lerner, Sandra, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 47)
        - Leventhal-Stern, Barbara, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 48)
        - Levy, Judy, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 49)
        - Lijn, Liliane, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 50)
        - Long, Mary Ellen, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 51)
        - Margolis, Judith Cohen, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 52)
        - Marsh, Cynthia, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 53)
        - Mealiffe, Mary, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 54)
        - Meise, Barbara, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 55)
        - Melhourne, Lise, BOE, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 56)
        - Montano, Linda, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 57)
        - Neaderlan, Louise, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 58)
        - Nolda, Rebecca, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 59)
        - Nunneley, Judy Stone, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 60)
        - Oliveros, Pauline, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 61)
        - Pond, Mimi, Davids, Betsy and Petrillo, Jim, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 62)
        - Prentice, Margaret, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 63)
        - Price, Robin, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 64)
        - Rahmani, Aviva, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 65)
        - Rexroth, Nancy, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 66)
        - Ringgold, Faith, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 67)
        - Rosenberg, Marilyn, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 68)
        - Rosenthal, Ann T., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 69)
        - Rosenthal, Barbara, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 70)
        - Rosenthal, Rachel, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 71)
        - Rosler, Martha, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 72)
        - Rowe, Sandra, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 73)
        - Saar, Betye, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 74)
        - Schwimmer, Sandra, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 75)
        - Sheridan, Sonia Landy, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 76)
        - Siberell, Anne Hicks, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 77)
        - Smith, Mimi, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 78)
        - Stensaas, Starla, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 79)
        - Stevens, May, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 80)
        - Sward, Marilyn, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 81)
        - Tetenbaum, Barbara, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 82)
        - Ting, Mary, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 83)
        - Turyn, Anne, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 84)
        - Underhill, Linn, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 85)
        - Weil, Susan, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 86)
        - Wilson, Diana, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 87)
        - Wilson, Martha, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 88)
        - Zweig, Janet, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 89)
    - Woodmansee Gift, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 63)
- Exhibition Files, 1979-2015, Accession 2015-042; 2 cubic ft. (2 boxes); Exhibition files from the Institute of Visual Arts, 1979-2015, including event calendars, catalogs, and other publicity.
  - Exhibition Brochures, Clippings, and Catalogs, 1979-2010 (1)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1986-2015 (2)
- Subject and Exhibition Files, 1991-2016, Accession 2016-011; 5 cubic ft. (5 boxes) 231 digital files (5.3 GB); The majority of the accession consists of files related to artists and exhibits from INOVA, including curator notes, exhibit planning, art images, exhibit images, and exhibit publications. A small amount of material is also included on the administration of INOVA, including directors’ correspondence, advisory board minutes, records from the annual Nohl Fellowship awarded by INOVA, and strategic planning documents. The digital files include video of and played in exhibits at INOVA, as well as photos of artwork and exhibitions.
  - Administrative/Subject Files, 1997-2014 (Box 1)
  - Artist and Exhibition Files, 1991-2015 (Box 2)
  - Artist and Exhibition Files, 2001-2010 (Box 3)
  - Artist and Exhibition Files, 2002-2015 (Box 4)
  - Exhibition Files and Publications, 1996-2009 (Box 5)
  - Exhibition Photos and Videos, 2003-2010